# 家里的狗狗很喜欢和我的拖鞋一起玩耍
my dog always likes to play with my slippers
# 但是普通的拖鞋质量有点差
but the quality of plastic slippers is not good enough
# 呐，玩着玩着就玩坏了，
well, the slippers are broken easily
# 不能够让它尽兴
the plastic slippers are not enough for my dog
# 所以我准备用油丝绳
so I want to prepare the wire ropes to make a pair of steel slippers
# 做一双“钢拖”
Let him play enough at one time
# 让他一次玩个够
(music)
# 音乐声
well, the pair of steel have been finished
# 呐，这双钢拖就算是完成啦
not only the pretty look but also the practical purpose
# 无论是从美观度还是从使用方面
which are so good
# 啊，我感觉都不错
now it is time to give them to my dog come here my doggy
# 接下来就看我们家狗狗喜不喜欢啦
come on
# 狗狗，狗狗狗，
look at the slipper for you
# 看给你做的拖鞋，不是喜欢咬拖鞋吗,来吃
dont you like to bite the slippers? Come to bite
# 特别好吃，吃啊
very good, bite them!
# 吃啊吃啊吃啊
come on
# 辜负了我一番好意
He betrayed my kindness
# 不喜欢吃
My doggy does not like it.